Shreehari J

Mentor Lead

Contact



8903437668



jshreeharijayavel@gmail.com



U-66, U block, Kovaipudhur Coimbatore - 641042

About me

I am a dedicated and experienced Lead Trainer with a strong background in on technical fields, specializing in online education and content development. With a total of 3 years and 6 months in the education and training industry I have honed my skits as a proficient educator, process trainer, and content developer. My career journey reflects a commitment to fastening learning retaining instructional methods, and cultivating engaging and effective educational expenses.

Languages

Tamil

Native

English

Advanced

Malayalam

Advanced

Achivements & Awards

- Attended national conference on the team IEEE Coimbatore - 641021.
- Played intern football semi final match in South zone for Rathinam Technical Campus.
- · Mini internship Java.

Education

2016-2020

BE-CSE

Rathinam Technical Campus

2015-2016

ΧII

C S I Boys Higher Secondary School

2013-2014

X

C S I Boys Higher Secondary School

Interests

Content writing, Quality analyst, SME, Data analyst, Software.

Work Experience

Focus Edumatics pvt ltd - 2020 - 2023 Full time

2022-2023

Mentor Lead

Maintaining team of 20-25. Guiding tutoring, Training new comers once they cleared certification, Subject Matter Expert, Quality Analyst, Leadership, Ed-Tech.

2021-2022

Senior tutor

K-12 education, Mathematics, Problem solving, Performance Motivation, Learning, Tutoring, Communication training, Team work, Ed-Tech,

2020-2021

Online tutor

Problem solving, Learning, teaching, tutoring, Online content, Communication training, SME, One to One, Chat process. Ed-Tech.

Skills

- Outlook configure
- Problem solving
- Strong communication
- Video/Audio teaching
- · Excel formulas
- Typing 60 WPM
- Quick learner